Hello
Здравствуйте
Hello from Ukraine, the city of
Здравствуйте из Украины город
Khmelnitsky And where are you from? I'm from Germany,
Хмельницкий А вы откуда Я из Германии
the city of Kalsura Are you a German citizen there
город кальсуру А вы там гражданин
or something like that? I was born in Germany
Германии или то да Я родился в Германии
Then then today I congratulate you on the holiday
Тогда тогда вас сегодня с праздником
Today is the day of the
поздравляю Сегодня же вас день
Reunification of the GDR
Воссоединения ГДР
[music]
[музыка]
[laughter] you
[смех]
work every day
каждый день трудишься
90 8  98 And how did your parents end up in
90 8 98 А как попали Ваши родители в
Germany
Германии
in 90 where
в 90 откуда
if it’s
если там
90 percent
90 процентов
like now
как вот сейчас
how can I tell you
как вам сказать
[music]
[музыка]
but I’m against this war Well,
но я против этой войны Да ну
we’ll probably have disagreements about who
наверное у нас будет разногласия кто
exactly is to blame for this war Yes, am I the one?
именно виноват в этой войне Да да я этот
I’m already getting ready  ask Yes, who is
ли Я уже готовлюсь спросить Да кто
to blame for the fact that Putin attacked Ukraine? I
виноват что Путин напал на Украину Я
think
думаю
that after all, 3 countries
что все-таки 3 страна
scolded the
поругали
Ukrainian Iran and China
украинские Иран и Китай
Iran China who
Иран Китай кто пору
is not equal at the time China And who scolded
не не равный Китай А кто поругал
Germany scolded Germany scolded
Германия поругала Германия поругала
Kazakhstan
Казахстан
Well, so you see or how I’m just not
Ну так вы видите или как Я просто не
quite
совсем
like well  that is, look, Putin is bombing
как ну то есть смотрите Путин бомбит
Khmelnitsky, mine is bombing Lvov, bombing is
Хмельницкий мой бомбит Львов бомбитки
bombing Mariupol, the faces of the earth
бомбит Мариуполь стерлись лица земли
have been erased Kharkov There they bombed a lot of people there, a lot of people left, that is, who from the USA forced
поуезжала то есть кто из США заставил
Putin Putin Well, they went and fired
Путина Путина Ну пошел постреляли
rockets, how it happened, tell me I
ракетами как это было расскажите
think that
Я думаю что
the hot phase began in the fourteenth
горячая фаза началась в четырнадцатом
year.
году
That is, it turns out  The USA said there Obama
То есть получается США сказала там Обама
then Moscow Putin Putin so Putin
тогда Москва Путин Путин так Путин
seize Crimea seize part of the Donetsk
захвати Крым захватить часть Донецкой
Lugansk region and then in 2021 I
Луганской области да а потом 2021 меня
won’t be there anymore, maybe it
уже не будет там же может быть так
all started with the Maidan and
все с Майдана началась
here, for
причем тут
example, there is a rally in Germany there
вот например митинге есть в Германии
is it
есть
happens
бывает это
activists activists Well, as it is now  not
активистых активисты Ну как сейчас не
often Listen, I don’t remember when we had
часто Слушай я не помню когда у нас были
you all the time their activists are blocking
у вас постоянно их активисты блокирует
something there are fighting at the May Day
что-то там бьются на Первомайской
demonstration the engine is like that yes These are
демонстрации движок такой да
your internal affairs We, for example, are
Это ваши внутренние дела Мы например из
not attacking you from this France is not
этого не нападаем на вас Франция не
attacking And now let’s explain it to me, a
нападает А теперь объяснил мне давай
German orc Yes  why then
немецкий орк Да почему тогда
The difference is that we
Разница в том что мы
don’t kick the government out of the demonstration, it’s
не выгоняем правительство с демонстрации
changing like this in Germany
меняется так Германии
and let’s say it
и что допустим
was like that then Poroshenko became Yes,
так было потом Порошенко стал
Poroshenko was elected in the elections
Да выборах избрали Порошенко на выборах
Poroshenko was elected in the elections and let’s say let’s
избрали Порошенко и допустим давай так
deal with Yanukovych now let’s say we
сейчас мы разберемся с Януковичем
kicked out the bailiff for example
допустим вот пристав мы выгнали например
we kicked out
мы выгнали
Yanukovych like this  and this one is on us, if you,
Януковича так и этот на нас вот если вы
for example, kick out Merkel, can
например выгоните Меркель Да может ли
France bomb, for example, Berlin or
Франция бомбить например Берлин или
Britain,
Британии
for example, it’s a violation of the Constitution you
например вот нарушение Конституции вы
kicked out. You’re a
выгнали
violation of the
Вот вы нарушение
Constitution. Can London bomb
Конституции Может ли Лондон бомбить
Berlin
Берлин
or seize it? It
или захватить там
can’t
не может
because it’s your internal affairs. You
потому что это ваш внутренние дела
want to expel what you want, you elected
хотите выгнали что захотели избрали
true,
правда
yes And now about Ukraine. For example, we
да А теперь про Украину Вот например мы
kicked out Yanukovych, we said Yanukovych,
выгнали Януковича мы сказали Янукович
part of the Ukrainian part,
часть украинского часть
not including people who are in Crimea,
не в том числе люди которые в Крыму
for example, right. Yes, look at the example
например правильно Да смотри на примере
in Germany, so people in a certain
в Германии так люди в определенной
area there in Munich will be there
области там в Мюнхене так будут там
against the Scholtz or for the sun.  you
против шольцы или за солнца Вот вы
drove out the Scholtz they will be
прогнали шольцы они
sewn up Can Italy then send troops
зашиваться Может ли Италия ввести войска
to Munich
тогда в Мюнхен
or Austria for example What example do
или Австрия например Какой пример вот у
we have here for example
нас например
Bavaria here in Bavaria you have something
Бавария вот в Баварии у вас что-то какие
you drove out for example the Scholtz and the leopard
вы выгнали например шольцы да барсом это
didn’t like it and Austria for example there is
не понравилось и Австрия например там
some artist taking it  and there will be troops
какой-то художник берет и будет войска
like in Munich,
типа в Мюнхен
not such an example
не такой пример
if For example, people in Bavaria were
если бы Например люди в Баварии были
against this,
против этого
going out on the street against going out on the street,
на улице выходить против вышли на улице
so Italy can lead troops to
так и Италия может вести войска в
Bavaria,
Баварию
wait, I’m waiting, no, I don’t want
мне подождите я жду Нет мне самый
Donetsk Lugansk, they can go out, they can go
Донецке Луганском могут выходить могут
to rallies, they can Russia Russia  On
на митинги могут Россия Россия 26
February 26, the admin of a building in Crimea was seized by the
февраля захватила админ здания в Крыму
Russian military Yes, airfields And so
российские военные Да аэродромы И так
on On what basis did one
дальше На каком основании одно
state seize
государство захватило
the territory of another state,
территорию другого государства
hiding behind the fact that people are people? For example, in
прикрываясь в том что люди люди Например
our Democratic country, people want to
у нас Демократическая страна люди хотят
go to rallies for the Maidan against
выходить на митинги за Майдан против
the Maidan, everything
Майдана все
fried the German
прожарил немецкого
as Poor thing is already shorter
как Бедняжка уже короче
Here you are, damn it, the badge came here, you are
Вот ты ваты блин понаезжала бляха вы
alive in the scoop in that convenient yesterday, damn it,
живы в совку в том удобном вчерашке блин
and in short, you came damn it carefully
и короче вы понаезжала блин внимательно
and brought with you
и Привезли с собой
and all those who grew up there attention against
и все те кто зарос там внимание против
Ukraine against Ukraine at the rally
Украины против Украины на митинга
tvtsvat, the scoop left
твцвата выехавшая Совка
the ass, lost their newspaper We are the truth and the
задницу потерял их газета Мы правда и
veins are shorter  damn in poverty Like all
жилы короче блин в нищете Типа все
the radiance when he left and he
радианс когда он выехал и он и хочет
wants to know Nostalgia Oh
хочет узнать Ностальгия Да капец
my gosh, who are people from Germany
мой кто люди из Германии
that are not like this
то не такой как этот
orc
орк
thank you so much to please support the
огромнейшее Вам спасибо до поддержите
armed forces of Ukraine
пожалуйста вооруженные силы Украины
because they are sitting like this, they only
потому что вот такие сидят они только и
dream Yes, so that Putin  captured Ukraine
мечтают Да чтобы Путин захватил Украину
Yes, they want Putin to come, that
Да они хотят чтобы Путин пришел что
Putin’s hide and seek came to Europe, they will
прятки Путина пришли в Европу они будут
justify everything later in any format,
оправдывать все потом в любом формате
so we must stop
поэтому мы должны остановить
every hryvnia of yours, every dollar of your
каждая ваша гривна каждый ваш доллар
euro, the victory of Ukraine means that Russia
евро победу Украины это то что Россия
will be stopped there in the east of Ukraine
будет остановлена там на востоке Украины
Yes, they are in the east of France
Да они на востоке Франции
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us through Kar Georgiev into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a very rich appearance is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
in order for the little operational little animal
для того чтобы мало оперативный зверезок
Sign right at a time and there are attempts there in a
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we are with you  stylish
информация и мы с вами по стильной
operational stars
оперативной звездок
Total type we will show you YouTube Glory to
Итого типа покажем вам YouTube Слава
Ukraine
Украине